#### SUMMARY

Not only do I have experience in multiple fields, but I am also going to school to develop new skills and love to learn new things. I'm a friendly person who enjoys meeting new people and working with others, but above all I want to find that forever-job that really works hard for me the way I work hard for it. I'm never afraid of a challenge and will always be excited to explore new information as it develops. I'm a nerd for technology and gaming as well as for all things science, but I also love numbers in general.

#### SKILLS

- Aloha systems/TSheets/CoConstruct /Navision/Business Central/IBS/Kronos /QuickBooks
- Excel/Sheets
- Word/Docs
- PowerPoint/Slides
- Outlook/Gmail/Dropbox/Drive
- Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, Edge
- Adobe Reader
- Accounts payables
- Accounts receivables
- Advertising
- Basic HTML/Javascript/CSS
- Bookkeeping
- **Business management**

- Cash handling
- Coaching/Staff Development
- Credit Reporting
- Customer service, Answering phones
- Data entry
- Event planning
- Faxing
- Filing
- General Ledger/Item Journals/GL Accounting
- Inventory control/Auditing/Pricing
- Merchandising
- Recruiting

#### ACCOUNTS RECEIVABLES SPECIALIST | 01/2019 to Current Straus Family Creamery - Petaluma, CA

#### Gmail>

Processing incoming check, ACH, wire and credit card payments from customers and Farmer's Market transactions into our accounting system.

Using Business Central and Navision systems.

Working with production, orders and warehouse departments to ensure paperwork and inventory accuracy.

Assisting with monthly inventory.

Processing month and reporting.

Tracking all AR including slow payments, Farmer's Market cash transaction logs, payment plans for past due items, customer returns and general invoicing.

Assisting with customer returns and courtesy/customer service credits.

Customer outreach for past due items on account and payment assistance issues.

#### **ACCOUNTING CLERK** | 01/2018 to 01/2019 G Family Construction Inc - San Rafael, CA

- Managing the accounts payable and accounts receivable for all four companies controlled by G Family (G Family Inc, G Landscape LLC, G Electric LLC, G Design LLC)
- Preparing billing for G Electric and G Landscape on a regular basis, sending out all maintenance billing monthly for G Landscape
- Answering phones for G Electric Maintaining all intercompany charges for subcontracting work between the companies, making all payments to vendors, performing bank transfers when necessary
- Assisting in maintaining all external property files for the owners when necessary

#### EXPERIENCE

- Assistance with system implementation, office coordination, event planning assistance Sales tax payments and recording through QuickBooks
- All overflow of basic office duties or needs
- Matching bank feeds daily
- Auditing all unclassified items in the chart of accounts and classing as needed, working closely with the hired CFO to maintain chart of accounts and set up new accounts as needed.

#### **ACCOUNTING CLERK** | 01/2016 to 01/2018

#### Chrisad Inc - San Rafael, CA

- Checking incoming accounting emails and processing requests from sales teams
- Preparing the payment sheet from the previous days sales as well as the daily production report and growth report
- Distributing invoices
- Processing daily accounts receivables orders
- Updating client files
- Processing billing each month as well as collection calls on delinquent accounts
- Processed new client agreements
- Closing out daily charges
- Following up on pending items with sales teams
- Auditing statements each month
- Creating and sending out collection and website deactivation letters for delinquent accounts
- Sending invoices and ledgers to clients when requested
- Coding credit card statements for processing
- Entering accounts payables items using general ledger strings
- Matching invoices processed for clients to invoices received from vendors for verification.

### ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT | 01/2015 to 01/2016 Floortex Design of San Rafael - San Rafael, CA

- Answering phones
- Faxing, filing, photocopying, scanning Invoicing and bookkeeping
- General cleanliness of showroom and upkeep
- Private labeling samples
- Tracking shipments
- Tracking projects with clients
- Checking in and checking out samples
- Merchandising of showroom tile department
- Greeting clients and referring them accordingly to sales team members
- Collaborating with admin at alternative showroom for invoicing and client referrals
- Interacting with reps from product lines we represent
- Assisting with pricing and sales where necessary
- Pulling dropped line items from sample collections.

#### ASSISTANT DEPARTMENT MANAGER | 01/2013 to 01/2015 Nordstrom Ebar - Corte Madera, CA

- Visual merchandising
- Training and recruiting new team members
- Coaching team members
- Making business decisions
- Advertising and promotion
- Managing cost of sales
- Accounting and bookkeeping
- Small business management.

#### **SHIFT LEAD** | 01/2010 to 01/2013

#### Peet's Coffee And Tea - Petaluma, CA

Coaching store cleanliness

- Stocking Organization
- Training new employees
- Cash handling/counting
- Supply ordering
- Managing staff on shift
- Inventory control
- Ensuring store policy as well as health and safety standards.

## OFFICE CLERK | 01/2010 to 03/2010 DB Claims Services - Rohnert Park, CA

• Purging old files Tracking files Data entry.

#### FILE CLERK | 06/2002 to 08/2002

#### Insurance Consulting Associates / DB Claims - Petaluma, CA

Purging old files, photocopying and data entry.

# EDUCATION AND TRAINING

#### Casa Grande High School - Petaluma, CA

General Education

Valley Oaks School - Petaluma, CA High School Diploma 09/2004

UC Berkeley Extension - Berkeley, CA

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp, Expected in 11/2021

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- I was published in the Immortal Verses Series from Poetry.com in 2006 for my poem "As I Stare".
- I served the homeless with Food Not Bombs in Santa Rosa.
- I teach knitting and crochet.
- I create and give away crochet and knit goods to those in need.

# ACTIVITIES AND HONORS

#### EbarFloortexChrisad

- I've served the homeless with Food Not Bombs in Santa Rosa, CA.
- I have crocheted for the homeless for years.
- I was published in the Immortal Verses series from Poetry.com in 2006 for my poem "As I Stare".
- I teach knitting and crochet.

### WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- www.linkedin.com/in/shannon-d-a9b518213
- live:.cid.f343c012891f4631